Athletics, Department of; Records ua746
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Photographs, 1955-2014; 9; 12.5 cubic ft.
  - Field Hockey [CD], 2002 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 24)
  - Football, 2002 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 25)
  - Football- Team Photo and Same, 2002 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 26)
  - Football vs. Central Conn. [CD], 2002 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 27)
  - Great Danes Awards and Dinner Digital, 2002 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 28)
  - Men's Lacrosse, 2002 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 29)
  - Men's Lacrosse [CD], 2002 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 30)
  - Men's and Women's Cross-Country [CD], 2002 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 31)
  - Men's Soccer [CD], 2002 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 32)
  - Men's Soccer [CD], 2002 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 33)
  - Softball [CD], 2002 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 34)
  - Track [CD], 2002 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 35)
  - Volleyball [CD], 2002 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 36)
  - Women's Basketball, 2002 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 37)
  - Women's Golf [CD], 2002 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 38)
  - Women's Lacrosse [CD], 2002 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 39)
  - Women's Soccer [CD], 2002 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 40)
  - Men's and Women's GROWL [CD], 2002-2003 (Box 8 (9-Photographs), Folder 41)
  - Men's Basketball [CD], 2002-2003 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Baseball [CD], 2003 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Field Hockey [CD], 2003 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - Football [CD], 2003 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Football-Team Photo, 2003 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Men's and Women's Cross Country [CD], 2003 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - Men's lacrosse [CD], 2003 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Men's Lacrosse [CD], 2003 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Men's Lacrosse and Baseball, 2003 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - Men's Soccer [CD], 2003 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Original proofs-Football, W.Soccer, M. Soccer, W. field Hockey, 2003 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - Softball [CD], 2003 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - Softball, 2003 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 13)
  - Track, 2003 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 14)
  - USA Basketball Women's National Team, 2003 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 15)
  - Volleyball, 2003 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 16)
  - Volleyball [CD], 2003 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 17)
  - Winter/Spring Sport Headshots Part 1, 2003 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 18)
  - Winter/Spring Sport Headshots Part 2, 2003 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 19)
  - Women's Lacrosse [CD], 2003 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 20)
  - Women's Soccer, 2003 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 21)
  - Women's Tennis [CD], 2003 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 22)
  - Assorted Headshots [CD], 2003-2004 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 23)
  - Brian Depasquale, Spring Sports Headshots, 2003-2004 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 24)
  - Baseball [CD], 2004 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 25)
  - Baseball, 2004 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 26)
  - Field Hockey [CD], 2004 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 27)
  - Men's and Women's Cross Country, 2004 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 28)
  - Men's and Women's Soccer, 2004 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 29)
  - Men's and Women's Cross Country [CD], 2004 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 30)
  - Men's Basketball [CD], 2004 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 31)
  - Men's Basketball vs. Sienna [CD], 2004 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 32)
  - Men's Soccer [CD], 2004 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 33)
  - Orchard Park Golf Course [CD], 2004 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 34)
  - Softball [CD], 2004 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 35)
  - Track and Field [CD], 2004 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 36)
  - Volleyball [CD], 2004 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 37)
  - Volleyball Set-Up [CD], 2004 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 38)
  - Women's Basketball [CD], 2004 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 39)
  - Women's Basketball [CD], 2004 (Box 9 (9-Photographs), Folder 40)
  - (Redone) Spring Invoice [CD], 2004 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Women's Soccer [CD], 2004 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Women's Tennis [CD], 2004 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball [CD], 2004-2005 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Men's Basketball, 2004-2005 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Track and Field Team Photos [CD], 2004-2005 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - Winter/Spring Sports [CD], 2004-2005 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Women's Basketball, 2004-2005 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Baseball, 2005 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - Baseball [CD], 2005 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Field Hockey, 2005 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - Field Hockey [CD], 2005 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - Great Danes Awards Lax team Turf Fields [CD], 2005 May 2; 2005 May 12; 2005 May 18 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 13)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball, 2005 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 14)
  - Men's and Women's Cross Country [CD], 2005 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 15)
  - Men's and Women's Headshots, 2005 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 16)
  - Men's and Women's Headshots, 2005 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 17)
  - Men and Women's Track A.East Champ [CD], 2005 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 18)
  - Men's Lacrosse vs. Bingo, Softball [CD], 2005 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 19)
  - Men's Soccer, 2005 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 20)
  - Rich Schmitt Photography [CD], 2005 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 21)
  - Softball 2005 A-East Championship [CD] (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 22)
  - Volleyball, 2005 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 23)
  - Women's Lacrosse vs. Siena [CD], 2005 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 24)
  - Women's Soccer, 2005 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 25)
  - Women's Tennis, 2005 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 26)
  - Headshots- Men's Lacrosse, ca. 2005 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 27)
  - Men's Basketball, 2005-2006 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 28)
  - Men's Basketball [CD], 2005-2006 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 29)
  - Women's Basketball [CD], 2005-2006 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 30)
  - Baseball [CDs], 2006 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 31)
  - Men's and Women's Track and Field 2006 America East Conference Championships [CD] (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 32)
  - Softball [CD], 2006 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 33)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 2006 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 34)
  - Volleyball, W.Golf, W. Field Hockey Champions, 2008; 2009 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 35)
  - Men's Outdoor Track and Field Champions, 2009 (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 36)
  - Headshots-Women's Lacrosse, ca. 2000s (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 37)
  - Lee McElioy, ca. 2000s (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 38)
  - Men's Track, ca. 2000s (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 39)
  - Opponents, ca. 2000s (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 40)
  - Women's Basketball Headshots, ca. 2000s (Box 10 (9-Photographs), Folder 41)
  - Football Game, ca. 2000s-2010s (Box 11 (9-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Football Player Portraits, ca. 2000s-2010s (Box 11 (9-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Football Player Portraits, ca. 2000s-2010s (Box 11 (9-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - Football Players Portraits, ca. 2000s-2010s (Box 11 (9-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Football Player's Portraits, ca. 2000s-2010s (Box 11 (9-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Football Player Portraits, ca. 2000s-2010s (Box 11 (9-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - Football Player Portraits, ca. 2000s-2010s (Box 11 (9-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Football Player Portraits, ca. 2000s-2010s (Box 11 (9-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Football Player Portraits, ca. 2000s-2010s (Box 11 (9-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - Football Player Portraits, ca. 2000s-2010s (Box 11 (9-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Football Player Portraits, ca. 2000s-2010s (Box 11 (9-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - Football Staff and Player Outings, ca. 2000s-2010s (Box 11 (9-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - Football North East Conference, 2011 (Box 11 (9-Photographs), Folder 13)
  - Football Team Captains, ca. 2010s (Box 11 (9-Photographs), Folder 14)
  - Brian Depasquale Phys Ed. 339 [CD], Undated (Box 11 (9-Photographs), Folder 15)
  - Brian Depasquale, Negatives, Undated (Box 11 (9-Photographs), Folder 16)
  - Cheerleading, Undated (Box 11 (9-Photographs), Folder 17)
  - Football, Undated (Box 11 (9-Photographs), Folder 18)
  - Football, Undated (Box 11 (9-Photographs), Folder 19)
  - Football Helmet Logo with logo sheets, Undated (Box 11 (9-Photographs), Folder 20)
  - Football Misc., Undated (Box 11 (9-Photographs), Folder 21)
  - Football Staff, Undated (Box 11 (9-Photographs), Folder 22)
  - Football Misc., Undated (Box 11 (9-Photographs), Folder 23)
  - Headshots, Undated (Box 12 (9-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Headshots, Undated (Box 12 (9-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Headshots, Digital, Undated (Box 12 (9-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - Headshots-Negatives, Undated (Box 12 (9-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Men's Football and Women's Soccer, Undated (Box 12 (9-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Printing Company Negatives, Undated (Box 12 (9-Photographs), Folder 6)
- Objects, ca. 1960-1990; 10; 5 cubic ft.
  The collection is unprocessed and is likely disorganized. Individual items may be difficult to find.
  Contains athletics memorobilia